<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Calma</string>
    <string name="forgot_pass">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="login_with_google">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="login_with_fb">Sign in with Facebook</string>
    <string name="signup_with_google">Sign up with Google</string>
    <string name="signup_with_fb">Sign up with Facebook</string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\'t have an account? Sign up</string>
    <string name="account_type_info">What does this mean?</string>
    <string name="dependant_hint">This account type means that you are likely using calma as you may
    find yourself in vulnerable positions in which you may require assistance from a "trustee". Having this account type will
    allow you to set a number of trusted contacts that you can request assistance from with three levels of severity. A typical dependant
    user would be a young child, a person with a disability or anybody who is likely to be put in a vulnerable situation. This could extend
    as far as somebody going on a blind date, who just wants peace of mind knowing someone will be there for them if things get murky!</string>
    <string name="trustee_hint">This account type means that you will be able to be assigned to one or more "dependant",
    where you will then be able to respond to their requests for assistance. You will be provided with different levels of analytics
    depending on the severity level of the request that is sent. A typical trustee user could be a parent of a child or somebody who is responsible
    for the wellbeing of another, such as a carer for people with disabilities or a carer for the elderly. </string>
    <string-array name="accountType">
        <item>Dependant</item>
        <item>Trustee</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="tracking_enabled_notif">Tracking is currently enabled. Tap to cancel.</string>
    <string name="test_email">test@test.com</string>
    <string name="test_password">testpassword</string>
    <string name="firebase_path">Location</string>
    <string name="title_activity_green_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_amber_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_google_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="dependant_dash_hint">\n- Calma is designed to help vulnerable people feel safe by being able to easily request help from people
    they trust.\n\n
        - If you press the GREEN button, this would indicate that you are okay and not in any dire need of help. A location marker of your position will be sent via text.\n\n
If you press the AMBER button, this would indicate that you feels unsafe or threatened, but is not in any ‘imminent danger’.
        - A personalised message will be included in the text that can be changed in the AMBER settings page.
        Hitting this button will also show you the local hospital and police stations.\n\n
        - Pressing the RED button would have the most consequences of all 3 buttons.
        This button is used for when you feel you are in imminent danger and need assistance immediately.
        When this button is pressed, the user’s GPS location is continuously sent out and it cannot be switched off without a password being entered correctly.
        A report will be compiled and sent to your trusted contact so that they can aid you effectively.
    </string>
    <string name="trustee_dash_hint">\n- Calma is designed to help vulnerable people feel safe by being able to easily request help from people
    they trust.\n\n
        - As a trustee, you can achieve this by having the ability to contact your dependants through a simple and easy interface. You can reach this interface
        by hitting the Contact Dependant button on your dashboard.\n\n
        - If you hit the Alert Tracker button from the dashboard, you will be able to see a log of all the times that your dependants have sent alerts,
        allowing an amalgamation of data for you to use to be able to help them in various ways - whether in the present or future.\n\n
        - Your own profile can be edited through the My Profile option on your dashboard, and you can add dependants to your account list from the
        Contacts interface.
    </string>
</resources>
